http://www.axiomgb.com/privacy-policy/

Open MenuTel: +44 (0)1827 61212Contact UsAxiom"Leaders in sorters, conveyors and mechanical handling systems"HomeOur Success StoriesSortation SystemsLynas FoodserviceCambridge AssessmentB2C EuropeSuperdrug DCGame GroupDDCCinram IberiaHealthspanPacking SystemsClick ‘n CollectUnipartAsdaAutomated Inline Packing SystemKuehne + NagelJD WilliamsUnipart Technology LogisticsConveyor SystemsKuehne + NagelAsdaFord Motor CompanyLakelandUnifixSpecial SolutionsTamar FoodsCinram IberiaPMSWhat our customers sayFAQsSortersPop-Up Roller SorterSwivel Wheel SorterAutomatic Pusher SorterSliding ShoePacking SystemsConveyor SystemCase, Carton, Parcel and Tote ConveyorsPallet Handling Conveyor SystemsSpecial SolutionsMechanical HandlingLabelling SystemsLogistics SoftwareControls & AutomationNewsroomLatest NewsBlogCase StudiesVideoImage GalleryAbout UsAxiom Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Notice shall become effective as of 25 May 2018.At Axiom, we understand that we have a responsibility to protect and respect your privacy and look after your personal data.For clarity, Axiom may be both data controller and data processor for your personal data under certain circumstances.We must advise that this policy is subject to change, so please check our website on a regular basis for any further changes.Data Protection law will change on 25 May 2018This Privacy Notice sets out your rights under the new laws.Who are we?Axiom is a provider of sorters, conveyors and mechanical handling systems, based in Tamworth. Axiom have a registered office at Axiom GB Ltd, Darwell Park, Tamworth, Staffordshire, B77 4DR, United Kingdom and company number 3787813. Matthew Nickson is the Data Protection Officer for Axiom.How the law protects youData protection laws state that we are only able to process personal data if we have valid reasons to do so. The basis for processing your personal data includes, but is not limited to, your consent, performance of a contract, to enable billing and remittance, and to contact you for customer service/support purposes.How do we collect personal data from you?We receive information about you from you when you use our systems, if you contact us by phone, email or otherwise in respect of any of our products and services or during the purchasing of any such product. Additionally, we also collect information from you when you sign up to our services or when you inform us of any other matter/s.If you provide us with personal data about a third party (for example when printing address labels for product/s for delivery during sortation), you warrant that you have obtained the express consent from the third party for the disclosure and use of their personal data.Your personal data may be automatically collected when you use our services, including but not limited to, your IP address, device-specific information, server logs, device event information, location information and unique application numbers.What type of data do we collect from you?The persona data that we may collect from you includes your name, address, email address, phone numbers, payment/ account information, social media and IP addresses. We also retain records of your queries and correspondence, in the event you contact us.Please be aware that content uploaded or otherwise made available by you onto your solution, whether published content or not, is not subject to our Privacy Notice.We merely process such data on your behalf, subject to our Terms and Conditions and you are responsible for any applicable legal requirements in respect of your content.How do we use your data?We use information about you in the following ways:To process orders that you have submitted to us;To provide you with products and services;To comply with our contractual obligations we have with you;To help us identify you and any accounts you hold with us;To enable us to review, develop and improve our services;To provide customer care, including responding to your requests if you contact us with a query;To administer accounts, process payments and keep track of billing and payments;To detect fraud and to make sure what you have told us is correct;To carry out marketing and statistical analysis;To notify you about changes to our services;Retention periodsWe will keep your personal data for the duration of the period you are a customer of Axiom. We shall retain your data only for as long as necessary in accordance with applicable laws.On the closure of your account, we may keep your data for up to 7 years after you have cancelled your services with us. We may not be able to delete your data before this time due to our legal and/or accountancy obligations. Data processed will be subject to your server/hardware decommissioning process. Axiom will not keep any data processed for research or statistical purposes.Who has access to your data?For the avoidance of doubt, we do not and never shall sell your data to any third parties for marketing or advertising purposes.We work closely with a number of third parties (including business parties, service providers) and we may receive information from them about you. These third parties may collect information about you including, but not limited to, your IP address, device-specific information, server logs, device event information, location information, and unique application numbers. We use their features within our company website to drive traffic (Google Ad Words), however, in some instances, they may be acting as data controller and they will have their own privacy policies, which we advise you to read.We will only ever share information about you that is necessary to provide the service and we have specific contracts in place, which ensure your personal data is secure and will not be used for any marketing purposes.We may share your personal data if we are under a duty to disclose data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Axiom, our customers, or others. However, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.however, it is not possible to gather information about other sites that have been visited prior to landing at www.axiomgb.com.Where we store your dataAll system information you provide to us is stored at our location. From time to time, your data may be transferred to and stored to a remote EEA location for Disaster Recovery purposes. By providing your data to us, you agree to this transfer and storage. However, we will ensure that reasonable steps are taken to protect your data in accordance with this privacy notice. Any sensitive data (your customers home address details for example) are stored on a secure local server interfacing with a Data Controller.LiabilityWe agree to take reasonable measures to protect your data in accordance with applicable laws and in accordance with our General Terms and Conditions.Data BreachesIn the event of a data breach, we shall ensure that our obligations under applicable data protection laws are complied with where necessary.CookiesCookies are used on this site; they are a common internet tool used to keep track of the information you have given us during your visits to the site. The cookie stored on your computer is simply a numeric identifier that we use to identify you as you move around the site and so you can conveniently retrieve information you have previously sent to our server.We use cookies to improve your experience on our websites and for functionality purposes;We also use cookies to understand your usage of our website;We have partners who have referred clients and in using cookies, we track referred traffic;We also use cookies for remarketing purposes, for example, once you have been on the Axiom website and then you visit another website which has Google adverts, you my see an Axiom advert to remind you of our products and services.Further information can be found at: http://www.ico.org.uk/for_organisations/privacy_and_electronic_communications/the_guide/cookies.aspx and http://www.allaboutcookies.org/Contact usPlease e-mail any questions or comments you have about privacy to us at info@axiomgb.comSocial@AxiomLeaders in sorters, conveyorsand mechanical handling systemsSEOXML Site MapLegal StuffPrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyPopular PagesLabelling SystemsMechanical HandlingSortersPacking SystemsLogistics SoftwareControls & AutomationAbout UsFAQsContact Us Axiom GB Ltd Darwell Park Tamworth Staffordshire B77 4DR United Kingdom
T: +44 (0)1827 61212Let's talk...We'd love to help solve your materials handling challenges - email us at: sales@axiomgb.com©2020 Axiom GB Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Registered in England No. 3787813.
Registered Office:
Ventura Park Road, Tamworth. B78 3HLHomeOur Success StoriesSortation SystemsLynas FoodserviceCambridge AssessmentB2C EuropeSuperdrug DCGame GroupDDCCinram IberiaHealthspanPacking SystemsClick ‘n CollectUnipartAsdaAutomated Inline Packing SystemKuehne + NagelJD WilliamsUnipart Technology LogisticsConveyor SystemsKuehne + NagelAsdaFord Motor CompanyLakelandUnifixSpecial SolutionsTamar FoodsCinram IberiaPMSWhat our customers sayFAQsSortersPop-Up Roller SorterSwivel Wheel SorterAutomatic Pusher SorterSliding ShoePacking SystemsConveyor SystemCase, Carton, Parcel and Tote ConveyorsPallet Handling Conveyor SystemsSpecial SolutionsMechanical HandlingLabelling SystemsLogistics SoftwareControls & AutomationNewsroomLatest NewsBlogCase StudiesVideoImage GalleryAbout Us
